http://www.glrrando.org/stats/pages/privacy.xhtml;jsessionid=1A6ACC332ADC76BAE29DEB3A994410E4

12/11/2020
GLR Home
HomeImperialsImperials HomeSubmit a New ImperialFind a ImperialReport a ImperialRide CalendarClubUpdate/Renew MembershipJoin Great Lakes RandonneursRide WaiverLeader ScheduleClub AdministrationStatsRides for 2020Ridden & WaitingJust turned inRides for the MonthTop Events for the YearGLR on the RoadMy ridesOthers on the roadLeadersPrevious YearsDistance BoardBiggest RidesLeader HistoryAdvice and TipsExpectationsNight RidingWeatherHow To Ride A BrevetRiding a Healthy RideSelf Reporting a BrevetGLR FAQFlèche/DartSafest Route PolicyTypes of GLR RidesAboutVolunteeringHow to VolunteerVolunteer Sign UpProcedures and Code of ConductCurrent Ride ProceduresSafe Cycling GuideCode of ConductSocial MediaGLR Google GroupGLR Facebook
Online Privacy Policy Agreement
RideStats LLC, (RideStats), is committed to keeping any and
all personal information collected of those individuals that visit
our website and make use of our online facilities and services
accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has
been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with
RideStats LLC of our commitment and realization of our obligation
not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply
toRideStats LLC , and thus it shall govern any and all data
collection and usage thereof. Through the use of
https://www.ridestats.bike you are herein consenting to the
following data procedures expressed within this agreement.
Collection of Information.
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the
privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use
or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other
websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
Use of Information Collected.
RideStats LLC may collect and may make use of personal
information to assist in the operation of our website and to
ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we
may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information
as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or
services that may be available to you from
https://www.ridestats.bike . RideStats LLC may also be in contact
with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research
questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential
future services that may be offered.
RideStats LLC does not now, nor will it in the future, sell,
rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third
parties.
RideStats LLC may disclose your personal information,
without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in
accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that
such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or
statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be
served upon RideStats LLC and/or our website;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or
property ofRideStats LLC; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to
safeguard the personal safety of users of
https://www.ridestats.bike and/or the general public.
Children Under Age of 13
RideStats LLC does not knowingly collect personal
identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen
(13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that
such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under
the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary
steps to ensure that such information is deleted from oursystem's
database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and
obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to
discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the
right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or
newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please
send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to Info@ridestats.bike.
If you wish to unsubscribe or opt- out from any third party
websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe
and/or opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other
websites.RideStats LLC does not claim nor accept responsibility
for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other
such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to
be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy
statements of each and every website that collects personally
identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy
Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by
our website.
Security
RideStats LLC shall endeavor and shall take every precaution
to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security
with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so
as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or
modification of the user's personal information under our control.
The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for
authentication and private communications in an effort to build
users' trust and confidence in the internet and website use by
providing simple and secure access and communication of credit
card and personal information.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
RideStats LLC reserves the right to update and/or change the
terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change
to our website homepage at https://www.ridestats.bike, so that our
users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information
we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if
any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time
RideStats LLC decides to make use of any personally identifiable
information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which
was stated when this information was initially collected, the user
or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time
shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of
their information in this separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting
the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned
Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our
terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of
our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website
following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and
conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of
such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy
Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to
contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing
address.
Email: info@ridestats.bike Telephone Number: 952-238-1102
Mailing Address:
RideStats LLC
2934 Virginia Ave S
St Louis Park, Minnesota 55426
12/24/2018
Show me my ridesTop Attended Rides for 2020Top Riders for 2020Just turned inMost Active Leaders for 2020Find rides in 2020Home
Copyright RideStats LLC and Great Lakes Randonneurs (Content), 2020
